[{"answer": "How you been", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "want to be reminded", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "My last compadre", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I have nothing to do with the news, Mr. my friend", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Not in her arms, in a sling across her chest.  In her , she had a MAC 10. Mr. my friend?  This is a friendly meeting, right", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "My handicap is I can't play golf", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I play with the best clubs money can buy. It's not the clubs, it's a woeful lack of talent", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What I'd like to know is if you'd ever seen Dr. my friend before the court assigned you to him for therapy", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That is what I mean, yes.  Weren't you both on the board of the that plac", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "that place.  I received it two weeks ago", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The package it came in...  question. I don't know.  There was nothing written on it of interest.  Did I throw it out", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't handle my friend memorabilia.  my friend memorabilia", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You're a policeman, of course you're confused", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Chief Inspector my friend of the Questura", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm investigating the disappearance of your predecessor, my friend. I was wondering i", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What?  No.  That I'm sure.  We my friend's victims.  He makes sure we find them", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Or she", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They didn'", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I believe my colleagues are checking suspects' homes to see if they have any my friend prints", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Serial killers are obvious.  Their primary  is to be obvious, to be noticed", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Is that an American accent, doctor", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I've always wanted to visit.  New that place especially", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How will you take him down", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's my business too", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We know about dangerous men around here, too, unfortunately", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "First of all, my friend, thank you for the wealth of wonderful items you've provided me from your personal Lecter treasure trove.  I've enjoyed them immensely", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, yes.  Please sit.  Yes, beside Dr. my friend is fine.  That's his real name, too.  There.  Good.  No", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, while you were working at the state hospital", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "- as an ", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That I don't think you'd like", "docId": "hannibal_production.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "It  good", "qsentId": 34}]